AKSHAY GOYAL

SUMMARY

Meticulous FullStack Developer with 8+ years of experience Developing, testing, and designing software solutions. In-depth understanding of web technologies with focus on delivering innovative business solutions. Excels in fast-paced, high-energy and deadline-driven environment with willingness to take on additional tasks.

EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Engineer FREELANCER | January 2020 - Current

- · Working as a freelance Lead Javascript contractor
- Product Name: Inkdesk(inkdesk.com)
- Skills: React with web Accessibility, Remix, Next.js, Prisma, MySql, Typescript, D3, CI, CD
- Brief: It's a platform where publishers do affiliate marketing for brands.
- · My key responsibilities are:
- Develop UI from scratch using RemixJs which follows best practices and standards
- Conceptualize original ideas that bring simplicity and user friendliness to complex design roadblocks
- Collaborate with product management and engineering to define and implement innovative solutions for the product direction, visuals, and experience

Lead Javascript Developer IMPETUS INFOTECH | July 2018 - December 2019

- Product Name: EGRC-Reporting
- Skills: React, Redux, MongoDB, Node.js, Docker, Typescript, Jest, Cubejs, Agile
- Brief: Central repository for risk dashboards across American Express with an option to preview and drag & drop and download charts.
- · My key responsibilities were:
- Develop UI from scratch using React-Redux which follows best practices and standards
- · Integration of GraphQl on the server side in express
- Working in the Agile/Scrum development environment and actively participated in scrum meetings.

Senior Software Engineer LINKITES INFOTECH | May 2016 - June 2018

- Product Name: LTC (lovethesecities.com)
- Platform & Skills: React, GraphQl, AWS (EC2), Typescript
- Brief: It is a project based on an express GraphQI framework
- In this people search for venues and concierges help them to make itineraries so it's like travel guide site
- Platform & skills: React, NodeJS, Docker, MongoDB

Software Engineer YUVASOFT SOLUTIONS PVT LTD | April 2014 - April 2016

- Worked as Fullstack developer on various web apps
- Platform & skills: React, NodeJS, ROR, Postgres, Sequlize, Git

CONTACT

akshay.goyal1008@gmail.com, +91-8109078749

CONTACT

- **3** +91-8109078749
- □ akshay.goyal1008@gmail.com
- ndore, INDIA 452009
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/akshay-goyal-49271366/
- https://github.com/akshaygoyal88

SKILLS

- Front-end: React, Redux, MERN stack, JavaScript, Accessibility
- Framework: NodeJS, ROR, Apollo, GraphQl, Remix
- **Programming:** Ruby, Javascript, Solidity
- Web Design: HTML5, CSS3
- Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.
- Version control: GIT, GIT-Repo
- Unit Test Cases: Jest, Enzyme
- **Deployment**: Docker, AWS (EC2), Nginx, Kubernetes

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Engineering RGPV